// creating an array and passing the number, questions, options, and answers
let questions = [
    {
    numb: 1,
    question: "Caesar Cipher uses C =(p+k) mod 26 to encrypt, where k=7. Use Caesarâ€™s Cipher to decipher the following:AYVQHU OVYZL",
    answer: "TROJAN HORSE",
    options: [
      "TROJAN HORSE",
      "BRUTE FORCE",
      "BRUTE HORSE",
      "TROJAN FORCE"
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 2,
    question: "A technology that hides information inside a picture, and follows the concept of security through obscurity is __?",
    answer: "Steganography",
    options: [
      "Rootkits",
      "Bitmapping",
      "Steganography",
      "Image Rendering"
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 3,
    question: "A technique used to identify live systems in a network?",
    answer: "ICMP Ping sweep",
    options: [
      "IP sweep",
      "ICMP Ping sweep",
      "Traceroute",
      "tcp ping scan"
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 4,
    question: "Having individuals provide personal information to obtain a free offer provided through the Internet is considered what type of social engineering?",
    answer: "Computer-based",
    options: [
      "Web-based",
      "Human-based",
      "User-based",
      "Computer-based"
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 5,
    question: "__________ is a popular open-source tool used for discovering a single host network or large networks as well as security auditing.",
    answer: "Network Mapper",
    options: [
      "Ettercap",
      "Metasploit",
      "Burp Suit",
      "Network Mapper"
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 6,
    question: "In which algorithm the 64 bit key input is shortened to 56 bits by ignoring every 8th bit.",
    answer: "DES ALGORITHM",
    options: [
      "AES ALGORITHM",
      "DES ALGORITHM",
      "RSA ENCRYPTION",
      "HASH FUNCTIONS"
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 7,
    question: "Which software is designed to enter the target's device, gather all information, observe all user activities, and send all information to a third party without your permission?",
    answer: "Spyware",
    options: [
      "Malware",
      "Adware",
      "Spyware",
      "Ransomware"
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 8,
    question: "An encryption scheme is _______ secure if the ciphertext generated does not contain enough information to determine uniquely the corresponding plaintext, no matter how much cipher text is available.",
    answer: "Unconditionally",
    options: [
      "Unconditionally",
      "Conditionally",
      "Computationally",
      "Relatively"
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 9,
    question: "Which one of the following options is not a part of the CIA Triad?",
    answer: "Authenticity",
    options: [
      "Availability",
      "Confidentiality",
      "Authenticity",
      "Integrity"
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 10,
    question: "Plain text are also called _________",
    answer: "Clear Text",
    options: [
      "Cipher-Text",
      "Raw Text",
      "Clear Text",
      "Simple Text"
    ]
  },
  // you can uncomment the below codes and make duplicate as more as you want to add question
  // but remember you need to give the numb value serialize like 1,2,3,5,6,7,8,9.....

  //   {
  //   numb: 6,
  //   question: "Your Question is Here",
  //   answer: "Correct answer of the question is here",
  //   options: [
  //     "Option 1",
  //     "option 2",
  //     "option 3",
  //     "option 4"
  //   ]
  // },
];

